Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1995 UE.4.1.6
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 6 Locals, 2.
  - Local 601
    - Local 601 General Incoming Correspondence, July 22, 1944 - August 1, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Barish to Marshall Dougherty Regarding Finances, November 20, 1944; 3. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 3)
      - Barish to Frank Panzino Regarding Finances, March 21, 1946; 4. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 4)
      - Barish to Ella Piazza Regarding Finances, April 30, 1946; 5. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 5)
      - Barish to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, July 24, 1946; 6. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 6)
      - Barish to Piazza Regarding Finances, July 31, 1946; 7. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 7)
      - Barish to Panzino Regarding Supplies, December 7, 1949; 8. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 8)
      - Barish to Piazza Regardinig Mailing List, May 29, 1952; 9. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 9)
      - D. Belling to Fitzpatrick Regarding Negotiations and Storeroom, November 11, 1948; 10. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 10)
      - William Cahn to Shirley Korn Regarding Labor History, March 23, 1946; 11. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 11)
      - Cahn to Fitzpatrick Regarding Wages and Supplies, May 5, 1946; 12. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 12)
      - Cahn to Marshall Thobois Regarding Publicity, January 18, 1950; 13. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 13)
      - Cahn to Panzino Regarding Publicity, July 28, 1950; 14. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 14)
      - Cahn to Fitzpatrick Regarding Inter-Union Rivarly, August 1, 1950; 15. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 15)
      - Cahn to Panzino Regarding Inter-Union Rivalry, August 1, 1950; 16. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 16)
      - James Carey to Fred Smith Regarding Factionalism, December 13, 1940; 17. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 17)
      - Carey to Walter Jackson Regarding Factionalism, December 19, 1940; 18. (Box 5, Folder 69, Item 18)
    - Local 601 General Incoming Correspondence, August 14, 1939 - November 27, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Julius Emspak to Local 601 Regarding Finances, August 14, 1939; 1. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Patrick Welsh Regarding Mailing List, September 13, 1940; 2-3. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 2-3.)
      - Emspak to Welsh Regarding Mailing List, October 10, 1940; 4-5. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 4-5.)
      - Emspak to Welsh Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 6. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Welsh Regarding Mailing List, November 8, 1940; 7. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Welsh Regarding Finances, November 8, 1940; 8. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 8)
      - Emspak to Welsh Regarding Change of Address, November 22, 1940; 9. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 9)
      - Emspak to Welsh Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1940; 10-11. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 10-11.)
      - Emspak to Welsh Regarding Finances, December 26, 1940; 12. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 12)
      - Emspak to William Simpson, January 22, 1941; 13. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 13)
      - Emspak to Hugh Boyle Regarding Association of Catholic Trade Unionists and Factionalism, March 18, 1941; 14. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 14)
      - Emspak to Logan Burkhart Regarding Burkhart's Jail Sentence, June 5, 1941; 15. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 15)
      - Secretary to Emspak to Simpson Regarding International Labor Divisions, June 26, 1941; 16. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 16)
      - Emspak to Simpson Regarding International Labor Divisions, July 3, 1941; 17. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 17)
      - Emspak to Local 601 Regarding Finances, November 11, 1941; 18. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 18)
      - Secretary to Emspak to E. H. Spillane Regarding UE News, November 11, 1941; 19. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 19)
      - Emspak to Welsh Regarding Change of Address, November 21, 1941; 20. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 20)
      - Emspak to Simpson Regarding Local Property, November 27, 1941; 21. (Box 5, Folder 70, Item 21)
    - Local 601 General Incoming Correspondence, January 23, 1942 - July 17, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - Julius Emspak to William Simpson Regarding Military Personnel, January 23, 1942; 1. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Simpson Regarding Staff Finances, February 13, 1942; 2. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Simpson Regarding Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Strike at Kirkland Lake, February 16, 1942; 3. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 3)
      - Emspak to E. H. Spillane Regarding Local Addresses, June 23, 1942; 4. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Stanley Glass Regarding Advertising, June 25, 1942; 5. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 5)
      - Emspak to Simpson Regarding General Executive Board Minutes, June 26, 1942; 6. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 6)
      - Secretary to Emspak Letter, September 9, 1942; 7. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Erwin Spillane Regarding Generator, September 18, 1942; 8. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 8)
      - Emspak to Henry Carter Regarding UE Convention Proceedings, October 15, 1942; 9. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 9)
      - Emspak to Simpson Regarding American Federation of Labor, October 29, 1942; 10. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 10)
      - Emspak to Simpson Regarding Finances, October 30, 1942; 11. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 11)
      - Emspak to Edward Miller Regarding Finances and Local 626, July 12, 1943; 12. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 12)
      - Emspak to Alfred Oyler Regarding Taxation and 1943 UE Convention, October 21, 1943; 13. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 13)
      - Emspak to Miller Regarding Staff Finances, January 4, 1944; 14. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 14)
      - Emspak to Charles Funk Regarding Staff Finances, May 12, 1944; 15. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 15)
      - Emspak to T. J. Fitzpatrick Regarding Factionalism and War Labor Board, June 3, 1944; 16. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 16)
      - Emspak to Fitzpatrick Regarding Meeting, June 1, 1944; 17. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 17)
      - Emspak to Miller Regarding Staff Finances, July 17, 1944; 18. (Box 5, Folder 71, Item 18)
    - Local 601 General Incoming Correspondence, July 18, 1944 - June 23, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Julius Emspak to Edward Miller Regarding Staff Finances with Receipt, July 18, 1944; 1. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 1)
      - Emspak to T. J. Fitzpatrick Regarding Staff Finances, October 6, 1944; 2. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Miller Regarding Staff Finances with October 3, 1944, Albert Olson Letter to Frederick Livingston, October 9, 1944; 3. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Micheal Fitzpatrick Regarding Staff Finances, December 1, 1944; 4. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Frank Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, January 31, 1946; 5. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 5)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, February 6, 1946; 6. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, March 18, 1946; 7. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, April 26, 1946; 8. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 8)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, May 8, 1946; 9. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 9)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, July 24, 1946; 10. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 10)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, August 23, 1946; 11. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 11)
      - Emspak Telegram to Panzino Regarding Meeting, October 22, 1946; 12. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 12)
      - Emspak to Richard Tobin Regarding Staff Finances, January 18, 1947; 13. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 13)
      - Emspak to Tobin Regarding Staff Finances, February 5, 1947; 14. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 14)
      - Emspak to Thomas Fitzpatrick, February 5, 1947; 15. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 15)
      - Secretary to Emspak to Tobin, March 25, 1947; 16. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 16)
      - Emspak to Phil Conahan and Louis Pogyor Regarding Staff Finances, May 7, 1947; 17. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 17)
      - Emspak to Pogyor Regarding Staff Finances, May 27, 1947; 18. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 18)
      - Emspak Telegram to Pogyor, July 1947; 19. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 19)
      - Emspak to Campbell Beveridge Regarding Staff Finances, September 19, 1947; 20. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 20)
      - Emspak to Pogyor Regarding Staff Finances, October 31, 1947; 21. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 21)
      - Emspak to Beveridge Regarding Staff Finances, January 14, 1948; 22. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 22)
      - Emspak to Beveridge Regarding Staff Finances, March 19, 1948; 23. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 23)
      - Emspak to Charles Copeland Regarding Staff Finances, June 23, 1948; 24. (Box 5, Folder 72, Item 24)
    - Local 601 General Incoming Correspondence, July 25, 1948 - December 8, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - Julius Emspak to Thomas Fitzpatrick, July 25, 1948; 1. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Charles Copeland Regarding Staff Finances, July 29, 1948; 2. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Fitzpatrick Regarding Staff Finances, October 25, 1948; 3. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Fitzpatrick Regarding Supplies, March 25, 1949; 4. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Frank Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, November 25, 1949; 5. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 5)
      - Emspak Telegram to Porter Mechling Regarding Meeting, January 5, 1950; 6. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, February 3, 1950; 7. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, February 10, 1950; 8. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 8)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, April 4, 1950; 9. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 9)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, April 20, 1950; 10. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 10)
      - Emspak to Mechleng Regarding Staff Finances, May 5, 1950; 11. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 11)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, May 11, 1950; 12. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 12)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, May 17, 1950; 13. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 13)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, June 2, 1950; 14. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 14)
      - Emspak to Ella Piazza Regarding Mailing List, June 6, 1950; 15. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 15)
      - Emspak to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, June 13, 1950; 16. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 16)
      - Emspak to Harry Nelson Regarding Staff Finances, October 17, 1950; 17. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 17)
      - Emspak to Louis Pogyor Regarding Staff Finances, December 14, 1950; 18. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 18)
      - Emspak to M. Y. Steinberg Regarding Staff Finances, February 19, 1951; 19. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 19)
      - Emspak to Patrick O'Connor Regarding Local 601 IUE Strike and Westinghouse Inter-Union Relations, December 8, 1955; 20. (Box 5, Folder 73, Item 20)
    - Local 601 General Incoming Correspondence, February 5, 1942 - January 24, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 74)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to F. Smith, February 5, 1942; 1. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 1)
      - Fitzgerald to L. J. Faschia Regarding Westinghouse Contract and Back Pay with August 27, 1942, Faschia Letter to Fitzgerald, September 1, 1942; 2. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 2)
      - Secretary to Fitzgerald, Ray Klausner, Telegram to Alfred Oyler, February 26, 1943; 3. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 3)
      - Secretary to Fitzgerald, Klausner, to Oyler, March 1, 1943; 4. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 4)
      - Secretary to Fitzgerald, Klausner, to Oyler Regarding Meeting, March 4, 1943; 5. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 5)
      - Secretary to Fitzgerald to Oyler Regarding Locals 601-610 Joint Forum, March 17, 1943; 6. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 6)
      - Fitzgerald to Oyler Regarding Local 601-610 Joint Forum, March 19, 1943; 7. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 7)
      - Secretary to Fitzgerald, Klausner, to Marshall Dougherty Regarding Banquet, October 20, 1943; 8-9. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 8-9.)
      - Fitzgerald Telegram to Richard Tobin Regarding Meeting, January 7, 1948; 10. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 10)
      - Fitzgerald to Thomas Fitzpatrick, February 24, 1948; 11. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 11)
      - Fitzgerald to Wilma Maroda Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, November 12, 1948; 12. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 12)
      - Fitzgerald Telegram to Philip Conahan Regarding Membership, August 18, 1949; 13. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 13)
      - Fitzgerald Telegram to Porter Mechling Regarding Inter-Union Rivalry, June 1, 1951; 14. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 14)
      - J. B. Forman to Stanley Glass Regarding National Labor Relations Board, May 15, 1944; 15. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 15)
      - Nat Geller to Leona Goldschmidt Regarding Staff Finances, April 7, 1943; 16. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 16)
      - Geller to Goldschmidt Regarding Supplies, January 25, 1943; 17. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 17)
      - Geller to Ella Piazzo Regarding Staff Members, January 24, 1945; 18. (Box 5, Folder 74, Item 18)
    - Local 601 General Incoming Correspondence, September 29, 1937 - March 4, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - James Matles to Margaret Darin Regarding Organization, September 29, 1937; 1. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 1)
      - Matles to Darin Regarding Nuttall Appropriate Unit, April 29, 1941; 2. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 2)
      - Matles to John King Regarding Staff Finances, May 23, 1941; 3. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 3)
      - Matles to John King, May 26, 1941; 4. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 4)
      - Matles to William Simpson Regarding Nuttall, National Labor Relations Board and Unit Determination, June 3, 1941; 5. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 5)
      - Matles to Simpson Regarding Nuttall, NLRB and Unit Determination, June 6, 1941; 6. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 6)
      - Matles to Simpson Regarding Nuttall and Benolite Contracts, June 20, 1941; 7. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 7)
      - Matles Telegram to Charles Newell Regarding Publicity, December 4, 1941; 8. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 8)
      - Matles to Newell Regarding Mid-West Organizers Conference, December 16, 1941; 9. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 9)
      - Matles to Newell Regarding Westinghouse Grievances, December 17, 1941; 10. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 10)
      - Matles to Newell Regarding Westinghouse Contract and Grievances, December 22, 1941; 11. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 11)
      - Matles to Darin Regarding Supplies, December 24, 1941; 12. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 12)
      - Matles to Darin Regarding Supplies, January 9, 1942; 13. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 13)
      - Matles to Simpson, January 19, 1942; 14. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 14)
      - Matles Telegram to Marshall Dougherty, January 11, 1942; 15. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 15)
      - Matles to Darin Regarding Supplies, January 19, 1942; 16. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 16)
      - Matles to Simpson Regarding Westinghouse Negro Employment Report, February 4, 1942; 17. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 17)
      - Matles Telegram to Darin, April 14, 1942; 18. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 18)
      - Matles to Simpson Regarding Staff Members, May 1, 1942; 19. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 19)
      - Matles to Simpson Regarding Wages, October 7, 1942; 20. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 20)
      - Matles to Justin McAghon Regarding Grievances and Wages, 1942; 21. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 21)
      - Matles to Alfred Oyler Regarding Steward's Council Meeting, February 19, 1943; 22. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 22)
      - Matles to Oyler Regarding Meeting, March 1, 1943; 23. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 23)
      - Matles to Thomas Fitzpatrick Regarding Reservations, March 4, 1943; 24. (Box 5, Folder 75, Item 24)
    - Local 601 General Incoming Correspondence, March 29, 1943 - July 29, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - James Matles to Afred Oyler Regarding Steward's Council Meeting, March 29, 1943; 1. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 1)
      - Matles to Logan Burkhart Regarding Burkhart and Darin Cases, July 31, 1943; 2. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 2)
      - Matles to Thomas Fitzpatrick Regarding Al Smith, July 14, 1943; 3. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 3)
      - Matles to Lottie Lieb Regarding Reservations, August 24, 1943; 4. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 4)
      - Matles to Frank Panzino Regarding Buffalo Organization and Staff Finances, December 12, 1946; 5. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 5)
      - Matles to Richard Tobin Regarding Staff Finances with Per Capita Delinquency, February 6, 1947; 6. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 6)
      - Matles to Philip Conahan Regarding Staff Finances, February 6, 1947; 7. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 7)
      - Secretary to Matles, Selma Trauber, to Campbell Beveridge Regarding Publicity, August 11, 1948; 8. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 8)
      - Secretary to Matles, Trauber, to Beveridge Regarding Publicity, September 23, 1948; 9. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 9)
      - Matles to Porter Mechling Regarding Taft-Hartley Board, November 10, 1949; 10. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 10)
      - Matles to Panzino Regarding Supplies, February 1, 1950; 11. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 11)
      - Matles to John Ragan Regarding Jack Sartisky, January 19, 1951; 12. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 12)
      - Matles Telegram to David Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, May 5, 1950; 13. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 13)
      - Matles Telegram to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, May 1950; 14. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 14)
      - Matles Telegram to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, June 2, 1950; 15. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 15)
      - Matles to Local 601 Regarding Staff Meeting, November 17, 1951; 16. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 16)
      - Matles to Organizers Regarding 601 Organization, February 1, 1952; 17. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 17)
      - Matles to George Gibbs Regarding Nuttall and Staff Finances, July 29, 1952; 18. (Box 5, Folder 76, Item 18)
    - Local 601 General Incoming Correspondence, May 18, 1944 - May 5, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - Edward Matthews Telegram to Frank Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, November 6, 1946; 1. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 1)
      - Matthews to Panzino Regarding Staff Finances, November 6, 1946; 2. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 2)
      - Matthews Telegram to Charles Copeland, April 15, 1949; 3. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 3)
      - Charles Newell Telegram to Margaret Darin Regarding Meeting, August 23, 1941; 4. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 4)
      - Russ Nixon to Campbell Beveridge Regarding Political Action Committee, October 24, 1947; 5. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 5)
      - David Ratner to Local 601 Executive Board Regarding Lost Time and Grievances, June 4, 1947; 6. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 6)
      - Ratner to Robert Logsdon Regarding Staff Finances with Worksheets, May 5, 1951; 7. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 7)
      - Jessica Rhine to Carl Fitzpatrick Regarding Regional War Labor Board, May 18, 1944; 8. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 8)
      - R. W. Gray to Philip Conahan Regarding Grievances, Westinghouse and Beaver Plant Bargaining Rights, April 1, 1947; 9. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 9)
      - J. W. Schaffer to Conahan Regarding Beaver Works and Transfer Requests, April 3, 1947; 10. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 10)
      - David Schribner Telegram to Beveridge Regarding Taft-Hartley, Federal Elections and Union Funding, July 21, 1947; 11. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 11)
      - Schribner Telegram to Beveridge, July 22, 1947; 12. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 12)
      - Schribner Telegram to Panzino Regarding Trial, March 13, 1951; 13. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 13)
      - Ruth Shubert Telegram to Lottie Lieb Regarding Reservations, August 24, 1944; 14. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 14)
      - A. N. Townsen Telegram to Darin, undated; 15. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 15)
      - Kathy Memo to Ray Regarding Officers, March 23, 1948; 16. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 16)
      - UE Telegram to Panzino, undated; 17. (Box 5, Folder 77, Item 17)
    - Local 601 General Outgoing Correspondence, June 10, 1941 - January 6, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 78)
      - Cubby Angelo to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members and IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, January 12, 1951; 1. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 1)
      - Campbell Beveridge to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, September 16, 1947; 2. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 2)
      - Beveridge to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 3, 1947; 3. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 3)
      - Beveridge to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 9, 1947; 4. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 4)
      - Beveridge Telegram to David Schribner Regarding PAC and Taft-Hartley, July 18, 1948; 5. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 5)
      - Beveridge Telegram to Schribner Regarding PAC and Taft-Hartley, July 22, 1948; 6. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 6)
      - Beveridge Telegram to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Local 601 Officers Election, August 10, 1949; 7. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 7)
      - Marshall Brayditch to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members and IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, January 1951; 8. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 8)
      - George Buck to UE, January 6, 1965; 9. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 9)
      - Logan Burkhart to Emspak Regarding Jail Sentence, May 28, 1941; 10. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 10)
      - Burkhart to Emspak Regarding Jail Sentence, June 10, 1941; 11. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 11)
      - Burkhart to James Matles Regarding Dismissals, June 27, 1943; 12. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 12)
      - Frank Burns to David Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, April 1, 1950; 13. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 13)
      - Henry Carter to Emspak Regarding UE Convention, October 14, 1942; 14. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 14)
      - Carter to Emspak Regarding UE Convention, October 22, 1942; 15. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 15)
      - Donald Conley to Congressmen Regarding Housing, December 20, 1952; 16. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 16)
      - Charles Copeland Regarding Factionalism, May 19, 1948; 17. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 17)
      - Copeland to Charles Newell Regarding Grievances, Slow Down, Factionalism and Speed-Up., May 13, 1949; 19. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 19)
      - Copeland to Fitzgerald Regarding Slow Down and Grievance, April 15, 1949; 18. (Box 5, Folder 78, Item 18)
    - Local 601 General Outgoing Correspondence, June 9, 1941 - July 25, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - Margaret Darin Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Generator, June 9, 1941; 1. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 1)
      - Darin to James Matles Regarding Overtime and Local 601 Westinghouse Contract, January 8, 1942; 2. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 2)
      - Darin to Matles Regarding Local 601 Westinghouse Contract, January 14, 1942; 3. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 3)
      - Darin to Matles Regarding Local 601 Westinghouse Contract, January 22, 1942; 4. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 4)
      - Darin to Matles Regarding Employment, Factionalism, CIO News, and Generator, March 3, 1942; 5. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 5)
      - Darin to Matles Regarding Employment and Anti-Communism, April 3, 1942; 6. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 6)
      - Darin Telegram to Matles Regarding Employment, April 14, 1942; 7. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 7)
      - Darin to Albert Fitzgerald, January 1951; 8. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 8)
      - Marshall Daugherty to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Collective Bargaining and Local 601 Officers, February 24, 1942; 9. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 9)
      - Darin to Edward Matthews Regarding White Collar Workers and Wages, March 4, 1943; 10. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 10)
      - Darin to Fitzgerald Regarding Banquet and Westinghouse Contract, October 13, 1943; 11. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 11)
      - Darin to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 601 Officers, January 3, 1944; 12. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 12)
      - Darin Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 601 Officers, January 1944; 13. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 13)
      - Darin to Julius Emspak Regarding Address, September 26, 1944; 14. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 14)
      - Betty Drake to William Cahn Regarding Publicity, July 25, 1950; 15. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 15)
      - P. J. Fasson to Emspak Regarding Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, Factionalism and Anti-Communism, January 3, 1941; 16. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 16)
      - L. J. Faschia to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, September 7, 1942; 17. (Box 5, Folder 79, Item 17)